KELSEY TAYLOR



CAREER OBJECTIVE

Quality Assurance Specialist training in web-development and seeking a future career in Software Engineering. Possess a tech foundation and 5+ years' experience answering client inquiries, preparing presentations, multiple forms of correspondence, working with data, and various computer systems. Possess a B.S. in Exercise & Wellness. Tech-moms graduate and currently enrolled in ongoing courses.



WORK EXPERIENCE

QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST

Rumple., St. George, UT

October 2021 - Current

- Perform daily manual testing for online software, includes current and recurring bugs
- Report bugs and issues to developers utilizing Trello & Loom software, includes thorough and clear steps to recreate issues

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

doTERRA International, Pleasant Grove UT

Jan 2018 - Jan 2020

- Took over 60 calls per shift, or 120 chats per shift (2 simultaneous chats), responded to emails via Outlook, provided basic computer and website troubleshooting
- Advanced commissions training aided members and fellow agents in understanding the finances around commissions

PHYSICAL THERAPY AIDE

American Fork Physical Therapy, American Fork UT Sept 2017 – Jan 2018

- Managed 25 patients per day between 3 therapists. Gathered, updated, and logged progress reports
- Headed company's social media (Facebook & Instagram). Created
 3½ minute promotional video for website using Premiere Pro
- Maintained discretion and patient confidentiality

HELP DESK SECRETARY

Media Center, Harold B. Lee Library, Provo UT

Aug 2015 - Sept 2017

- Typed documents such as correspondence, memos, and emails, and prepared monthly presentations for employee trainings
- Supervised and trained Help Desk Clerks (9-12 per semester)
- Data management for 10,000+ DVDs, Audiobooks, VHS with Excel and Google Sheets
- Logged occupancy statistics for the department using Excel



CONTACT

Email:

kelseytay94@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/kelsey-taylor94



SOFT SKILLS

Time Management

Adaptable Fast Learner

Problem Solving

Strong Work Ethic

Positive & Cheerful Attitude



HARD SKILLS

Microsoft Office Suite

Adobe

HTML, CSS

JavaScript (Introduction)

Web / Tech Savvy

Typing Speed 90 WPM



EDUCATION

B.S. Exercise & Wellness

[April 2019]

Brigham Young University Provo, UT GPA: 3.81

Tech-Moms [Fall 2021]

Technical skills course in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript; introduction to cybersecurity, data analytics & reporting, product/project management, quality assurance, digital marketing, and UX/UI design.

SLCC Web-Development [Est.

Completion May 2022]
Course designed to teach HTML,

CSS, JavaScript, Wordpress, PHP/MYSQL